let questions = [
    {
        question: "When Michael Jordan returned to basketball in 1995, he released a statement to the media. what did the statement say?",
        answers: {
            a: "I'm back",
            b: "Lets go win a championship",
            c: "I'm here to win",
            d: "I'm better at basketball than baseball"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Where did Jurgen Klopp start his managerial career?",
        answers: {
            a: "Bayer Leverkusen",
            b: "Oktoberfest",
            c: "Mainz",
            d: "Borussia Dortmund"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which cricketer has taken the most test wickets?",
        answers: {
            a: "Shane Warne",
            b: "Glen McGrath",
            c: "Muthiah Muralitharan",
            d: "Eddie the eagle"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Who did Muhammad Ali fight in rumble in the jungle?",
        answers: {
            a: "Jason Bourne",
            b: "George Foreman",
            c: "Larry Holmes",
            d: "Joe Frazier"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "In which sport would you commonly use the terms: Chukka, Neckshot and Millionaires shot?",
        answers: {
            a: "Polo",
            b: "Bowls",
            c: "Volley Ball",
            d: "Rugby"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which formula 1 team did Lewis Hamilton compete for from 2007 to 2012?",
        answers: {
            a: "Mercedes",
            b: "Ferrari",
            c: "Vauxhall",
            d: "McLaren"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "What sport did Princess Anne compete in at the 1976 summer Olympic games?",
        answers: {
            a: "Judo",
            b: "Equestrian",
            c: "Dressage",
            d: "Gymnastics"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "How many Olympic gold medals did Michael Phelps win?",
        answers: {
            a: "23",
            b: "25",
            c: "21",
            d: "1"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which female tennis player has won the most grand slams?",
        answers: {
            a: "Venus Williams",
            b: "Margaret Court",
            c: "Serena Williams",
            d: "Kim Kardashian"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Which golfers have won the most PGA Tour events with 82 wins each?",
        answers: {
            a: "Tiger Woods & Jack Nicklaus",
            b: "Jack Nicklaus & Nick Faldo",
            c: "Tiger Woods & Sam Snead",
            d: "Phil & Grant Mitchell"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Where did Sir Alex Ferguson start out his managerial career?",
        answers: {
            a: "St Mirren",
            b: "Aberdeen",
            c: "Mardy FC",
            d: "East Stirlingshire"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the Premier Leagues all time top goal scorer?",
        answers: {
            a: "Dean Windass",
            b: "Alan Shearer",
            c: "Harry Kane",
            d: "Wayne Rooney"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What was Usain Bolts 100 meters record breaking time?",
        answers: {
            a: "45 Seconds",
            b: "10.05 Seconds",
            c: "9.58 Seconds",
            d: "9.89 Seconds"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What year did England win the rugby world cup?",
        answers: {
            a: "2003",
            b: "2007",
            c: "1966",
            d: "2022"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the leading all time try scorer for Wales in rugby?",
        answers: {
            a: "George North",
            b: "Shane Williams",
            c: "Gareth Thomas",
            d: "Hugh Llewellyn"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
]